Finding Aid for School of Public Health (University of Michigan) Records 1909-2015 (bulk 1941-2006).
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Dean Noreeen M. Clark, 1994-2004
  - Annual Files, 2002
    - University
      - Horace H. Rackham Graduate School, 2002 (Box 81)
      - General, 2002 (Box 81)
      - News and Information Services, 2002 (Box 81)
      - Office of the Provost, (Paul Courant) (Box 81)
      - Office of the Executive Vice President for Academic Affairs, (Paul Courant), 2002 (Box 81)
      - Office of the Executive Vice President for Research, (Fawwaz T. Ulaby), 2002 (Box 81)
      - Regents, 2002 (Box 81)
  - Annual Files, 2003
    - Administration
      - Academic Services, 2003 (Box 81)
      - Bioterrorism
        - Academic Center for Public Health Preparedness, 2003 (Box 81)
        - Center for Bioterrorism, 2003 (Box 81)
        - Martin, Jennifer, 2003 (Box 81)
      - Communications, Terri Mellow, 2003 (Box 81)
      - Community-Based Public Health, 2003 (Box 81)
      - Correspondence
        - American Public Health Association (APHA), 2003 (Box 81)
        - General
          - A-E, 2003 (Box 81)
          - F-K, 2003 (Box 81)
          - L-Q, 2003 (Box 81)
          - R-Z, 2003 (Box 81)
        - Foreign, 2003 (Box 81)
      - Development Office (Box 82)
        - General, 2003; 4 folders (Box 82)
        - Dean's Advisory Council, 2003 (Box 82)
        - Alumni Board of Governors, 2003 (Box 82)
      - Events
        - SPH Faculty Retreat, April 28, 2003 (Box 82)
      - Faculty
        - Alexander, Jeff, and Cathleen Connell, 2003 (Box 82)
        - Gray, Robert and Martin Philbert, 2003 (Box 82)
      - Memos to Dept. Chairmen, 2003 (Box 82)
      - Prevention Research Center, 2003 (Box 82)
      - Public Health Information Services and Access, 2003 (Box 82)
      - Recruitment, 2003 (Box 95)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2033 ]
      - State of the School Presentations, 2003 (Box 82)
      - Students, 2003 (Box 95)
    - Committees
      - Executive Committee, 2003 (Box 82)
      - Faculty Meetings, 2003 (Box 82)
      - General, 2003 (Box 82)
      - Strategic Planning Committee, 2003 (Box 82)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics
        - General, 2003 (Box 82)
        - Little, Roderick, 2003 (Box 82)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health
        - General, 2003 (Box 82)
        - Vincent, James, 2003 (Box 82)
        - EHS External Review, 2003 (Box 82)
      - Epidemiology
        - General, 2003 (Box 82)
        - Morgenstern, Hal, 2003 (Box 82)
        - Schottenfild, David, 2003 (Box 82)
        - Kaplan, George, 2003 (Box 82)
      - Health Behavior and Health Education
        - General, 2003 (Box 82)
        - James, Sherman, and Mark Zimmerman, 2003 (Box 82)
        - Caroline Wang's Grant, 2003 (Box 82)
      - Health Services Management and Policy
        - General, 2003 (Box 82)
        - Smith, Dean, 2003 (Box 82)
        - Wessert, Bill, 2003 (Box 82)
      - Population Planning and International Health
        - Center for Population Planning, 2003 (Box 82)
    - National
      - Washington D.C.
        - Public Health Service (includes Center for Disease Control correspondence), 2003 (Box 82)
    - State
      - Michigan Center for Health Interventions External; Advisory Committee, 2003 (Box 82)
    - University
      - Center for Human Growth and Development Advisory Committee, 2003 (Box 82)
      - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching, 2003 (Box 82)
      - Health Sciences Council, 2003 (Box 82)
      - Health Services Research Initiative, 2003 (Box 82)
      - Horace H. Rackham Graduate School, 2003 (Box 82)
      - Life Sciences Commission, 2003 (Box 82)
      - Office of the Provost, (Paul Courant), 2003 (Box 82)
      - Office of the Executive Vice President for Academic Affairs, (Paul Courant), 2003 (Box 82)
      - Office of the Executive Vice-President for Development, (Susan F. Feagin), 2003 (Box 82)
      - Office of the Executive Vice President for Research, (Fawwaz T. Ulaby), 2003 (Box 82)
      - Other Schools and Colleges, 2003 (Box 82)
      - Reproductive Sciences Program, 2003 (Box 82)
      - Regents, 2003 (Box 82)
  - Annual Files, 2004
    - Administration
      - Bioterrorism
        - Bioterrorism Search (Box 83)
        - Academic Centers for Public Health Preparedness Site visit, Atlanta, GA, 2004 (Box 83)
    - Council on Education for Public Health (CEPH) Accreditation
      - Accreditation Site Visit, March 30-April 1, 1992 (Box 83)
      - Board of Councilor's Meeting, June 9, 2000 (Box 83)
      - Correspondence
        - 1992-1997, 9 folders (Box 97)
        - 2000, 6 folders (Box 83)
- Archived School of Public Health Website
  The Archived Website series documents the academic programs, accomplishments, resources, events, and people at the School of Public Health. Content includes important news and announcements, publications (such as newsletters and course catalogs), and information about admissions, curriculum, degree requirements, faculty, and the overall mission of the School. The website series is arranged chronologically, with captures from 1997 to 2015. Starting in 2010, this archived website has been captured on a regular, ongoing basis as part of the University of Michigan Web Archives.
  - School of Public Health
    - 1997-2015
      (These versions were preserved by the Internet Archive and are made available through its Wayback Machine. The Bentley Historical Library is not involved in the collection or maintenance of this material.)
    - May 15, 2002, .ZIP file
    - May 22, 2003, .ZIP file
    - May 19, 2006, .ZIP file
    - May 6, 2008, .ZIP file
    - 2010-2015
  - Archived websites related to the School of Public Health, 2010-2015
- Photographs
  The Photographs series, 0.5 linear feet, includes positive prints and negatives documenting the administrators, faculty, and students of the school and some of their activities. The bulk of the material dates to the period between 1991 and 1996. The career and activities of David Striffler, pioneer in the field of dental public health, are represented strongly. A few records regarding Striffler's service to the public health community have been included in the folder containing his photographs in order to preserve the context of the record.
  - Class of 1968 (Box 97)
  - Events
    - Convocation, 1991 (Box 97)
    - General, 1991; 1996; undated (Box 97)
  - Faculty and Administrators
    - General and undated, 1960-1997; 3 folders (Box 97)
    - Headshots, 1984; 1993; 1994; undated (Box 97)
    - Striffler, David 19751985, 1960; undated (Box 97)
  - Students, 1995 (Box 97)
  - Negatives, 1925; 1938-1939; 1994-1996 (Box 97)